http://www.humaneticscorp.com/privacy-policy

Copyright 2016Privacy PolicyTerms of UseSign InHomeAbout UsAbout Us OverviewKey MilestonesLeadershipLeadership OverviewRonald ZenkJohn DykstraMark PayneMichael Kaytor, Ph.D.Theodore JohnsonJames Behnke, Ph.D.Richard NealZeljko Vujaskovic, M.D.Robert Miller, M.D.Matthew L. Nathan, M.D.Colin G. Chinn, M.D.Isabel Jackson, Ph.D.Michael Landauer, Ph.D.Ronald J Manning, Ph.D.Collaboration PartnersIntellectual PropertyOur TechnologyOur Technology OverviewRadiation ModulatorsMechanism of ActionSafety and ToxicologyPharmacokineticsRelevant PublicationsOur FocusOur Focus OverviewPipelineOncologyOncology OverviewNon-Small Cell Lung CancerHead and Neck CancersProstate CancerInflammatory Lung DiseasesMedical CountermeasuresNewsContact Us
Privacy PolicyWe respect the privacy of our visitors to our website, the home page of which is located at www.humaneticscorp.com. This Privacy Policy is intended to inform you of our policies and practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of any personal information you submit to us through our website. "Personal Information" is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and other information that is not otherwise publicly available.
User Consent
By submitting Personal Information through our website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.
Collection of Personal Information
We collect Personal Information that you submit to us voluntarily through our website. The types of Information we collect are:
For visitors who email us directly via an email hyperlink:
Email address
Any content included in the email
For all visitors: As you navigate our website, certain passive information will also be collected, including Internet Protocol addresses, cookies and navigational data. This type of information will be used for the purposes of gathering data to provide improved administration of our website, and to improve the quality of your experience when interacting with our website.
Use of Personal Information
In general, Personal Information you submit to us is used either to respond to requests that you make, or to aid us in serving you better.
Disclosure of Personal Information
We do not sell your Personal Information or share your information with other companies or organizations without your consent. The content of any communications you send to us is non-confidential, and we are under no obligation to refrain from reproducing, publishing, or otherwise using such content in any way or for any purpose. We will not reproduce, publish, or otherwise use your Personal Information in connection with such content. We may, however, reproduce or use your Personal Information in connection with any resume you submit to us for employment recruiting purposes. We are free to use the content of any such communications (excluding any resume you submit to us), including any ideas, inventions, concepts, techniques, or know-how disclosed therein, for any purpose including developing, manufacturing, and/or marketing goods or services.
We may share some or all of your Personal Information with affiliates we control such as wholly-owned subsidiaries, in which case we will require our affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy. If we are acquired by another company, that company will possess the Personal Information collected by us and it will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy.
Links to Other Sites
Our provision of a link to any other website or location is for your convenience and does not signify our endorsement of such other website or location or its contents. We have no control over, do not review, and cannot be responsible for, these outside websites or their content. Please be aware that the terms of our Privacy Policy do not apply to these outside websites.
Data Security
We use industry-standard methods to secure the communication of Personal Information from your computer to our servers. In addition, we use industry-standard methods of securing our databases of Personal Information, including the use of firewalls. Except as provided elsewhere in this Privacy Policy, we limit access to Personal Information databases to those persons in our organization that have a business need for such access. You should know, however, that no company, including Humanetics Corporation, can fully eliminate security risks associated with Personal Information.
Contact Us
Should you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us using the Contact Us section of this website or write us at:
Humanetics Corporation7650 Edinborough Way, Suite 620 Edina, MN 55435
Privacy Policy Updates
This Privacy Policy is subject to occasional revision, and any changes will be posted on this site. If you object to any such changes, you must cease using our website. Continued use of our website following notice of any such changes shall indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes. This policy was last updated on July 6, 2016.
